fhtm.net 2012-06-05

# Privacy Policy - Fortune Hi-Tech Marketing

  1. Definition of Policy & Revision Date
  2. Method for Collection of Information
  3. What we do with that information
  4. Security of information
  5. Other websites
  6. Commitment to Security & Privacy
  7. Acceptance of Policy, subject to change
  8. Contact Information

## 1\. Definition of Policy & Revision Date

This Privacy Protection Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes our privacy collection and protection policies and those of our affiliates. This Privacy Policy was last revised August 13, 2004. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to people that we do not employ or manage. In addition, certain companies with whom we contract have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on links on such companies' websites. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This privacy policy applies to all of the websites owned by us and describes the methods for collection, storage and use of personally identifiable information. As used herein, "personally identifiable information" means any non-public information that that would enable us or a third party to identify or contact you by electronic or other means. We encourage you to carefully read this privacy policy in its entirety. 

## 2\. Method for Collection of Information

We collect non-public personally identifiable information by asking you for it when you order or signup for a service and when you contact technical support or customer service. Such information may include your name, physical address, telephone number, credit card or bank account information and/or email address. We may share this information with our commonly owned affiliates. We may also receive similar information from our strategic partners that have already obtained information from and/or about you in accordance with their respective agreements with you and we may combine information that we receive from you with information that we receive from our strategic partners or others. Once you register with us, you are not anonymous to us. We may also use "cookies" and similar technology to obtain information about your visits to our sites. While cookies help us improve your experience while visiting our sites, you may block them through your Internet browser or other commercially available software. However, in doing so, you may make some of our sites' features no longer accessible. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, our cookie information and the pages you request. 

## 3\. What we do with Non-Public Personally Identifiable Information

We use the personally identifiable information we collect principally to provide you with the service(s) you have ordered, to collect payment from you on account of the services that you receive from us and to let you know about other offerings which may be of interest to you. Postal and e-mail address information, for example, enables communication about services offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services. Like most businesses today, we use third-party vendors to carry out certain functions and the delivery of certain services to you. And like most businesses today, we share online data with those third-party vendors to the extent necessary for them to perform their work. For example, we may use a third-party payment processing company in order to process credit card payments. In such an instance, we will share your personally identifiable information in order to verify the credit card account information that you have submitted to us. We contractually require such third-party vendors to use personally identifiable information that we share with them only for the purpose(s) for which it was shared. We also contractually require such entities to protect such information from any further or otherwise improper use. In addition, we may share such information with other industry and credit-related organizations to improve operations and to protect against fraud, security and credit risks. We do not otherwise rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * From time to time, we may provide personally identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands from law enforcement agencies or in response to court orders.
  * We may also use or disclose personally identifiable information when we believe that this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with or improperly using our property or services, or interfering with our customers' or others' use of our property or services.
  * We may use the email address you provide to give you product announcements, service updates or additional information that you may request.
  * In the future, should we decide to share such data with third parties for marketing, it will provide notification to you and will give you the opportunity to indicate whether you would prefer that we not provide such information about you to third parties.
  * Because this information is a critical part of our business, in the event of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding involving our company or companies, your personally identifiable information would be treated like our other assets (and could be transferred along with our other business assets). In this event, we will notify you before information about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We do not market to, or knowingly collect personal information from, children under the age of 13 on any of its websites. 

## 4\. Security of information

All personally identifiable information is maintained in secure databases. We use multiple layers of encryption, firewalls and other technology to ensure the security of your personal information, and to prevent unauthorized access or improper use. 

## 5\. Other websites

Some links on our websites may take you to websites operated and/or controlled by third parties. As you surf the web, please be mindful of the respective identifications of the entities operating the websites that you visit and remember that we have no control over the collection or use of information on third-party websites, or the use of any personal information that you may provide in connection with the use of such websites. 

## 6\. Commitment to Security & Privacy

We are committed to maintaining the security of your personally identifiable information and promoting trust and confidence on the Internet. 

## 7\. Acceptance of Policy, subject to change

We reserve the right to revise or modify this policy, or any other policies or agreements at any time without prior notification. By using our services, you accept the terms and conditions of this policy.

## 8\. Contact Information

As a customer, you are able to modify your personally identifiable information online. If you do not have access to the internet for any reason or do not know where to go to view and/or modify your information, feel free to contact our Client Relations department using the information that follows. 

For questions regarding this policy, please contact:  
Fortune Hi-Tech Marketing, Inc.  
Customer Support  
880 Corporate Drive  
Lexington, KY 40503  
Phone: (859) 422-7008  
Fax: (859) 422-7036
